Guide to the CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records, 1857-2010 AIS.1991.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Survey Books, 1880s-1990s; XVI.
  - Mines, A-Z, 1.
    - Crescent Mine book no. 877; Outside notes, Division No. 13; Eclipse Mine (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 881; Outside notes, Division No. 13; Eclipse Mine, Vigilant Mine; Gas well locations, Property surveys, Lines and levels (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 904; Outside notes, Division No. 13; Property lines and levels, Building locations (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 912; Outside notes, Division No. 13; Eclipse Mine; Property lines and levels, Gas well locations (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 928; Outside notes, Division No. 13; Eclipse Mine (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 943; Outside notes, Division No. 13; Eclipse Mine (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 948; Outside notes, Division No. 13; Eclipse Mine, Dawson Mine (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1179, 1212 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1213, 1214 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1215, 1218 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1222, 1223 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1225, 1267 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1268, 1288 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1290, 1293 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1337, 1338 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1496, Eclipse Mine; Crescent Mine book no. 1504, room notes (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1523, 1705 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Crescent Mine book no. 1713; Inside notes; Crescent Mine, Air shaft side, book no. 4 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Crescent Mine # 1, book no. 1622, room notes; Crescent Mine # 1, book no. 1654, room notes (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Crescent Mine # 1, No. 2, book no. 4029; Crescent Mine # 1, No. 2, book no. 4029; Outside notes, Division No. 7 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, circuit book no. 1; Crescent Mine # 2, level book no. 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, methane book no. 1; Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, property book no. 1; Crescent Mine No 2, room book no. 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, stadia book no. 1; Crescent Mine # 2, transit book no. 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, level book no. 2; Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, room book no. 2; Crescent Mine # 2, strip book no. 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, transit book no. 2; Crescent Mine # 2, book no. 3 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, level book no. 3; Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 3 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, room book no. 3; Crescent Mine # 2, strip book no. 3 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, transit book no. 3; Crescent Mine # 2, level book no. 4 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 4; Crescent Mine # 2, transit book no. 4 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, level book no. 5; Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 5 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, transit book no. 5; Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 6 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, transit book no. 6; Crescent Mine # 2, No. 3, miscellaneous book no. 7 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 8; Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 9 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, miscellaneous book no. 10; Crescent Mine # 2, book no. 1596 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, book no. 1597; Crescent Mine # 2, book no. 1598 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Crescent Mine # 2, strip plant; Crescent Mine # 3, book no. 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Darr Mine book no. 22, 116 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Darr Mine book no. 160, 237 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Darr Mine book no. 282, topography; Darr Mine book no. 405, room book (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Darr Mine book no. 463, 1020 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Delmont Mine book no. 1107, 1112 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Delmont Mine book no. 1129, 1130 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Delmont Mine book no. 1134, 1140 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Delmont Mine book no. 1275; Delmont Mine book no. 1276, level notes (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Delmont Mine book no. 1298, 1444 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Delmont Mine book no. 1461, levels; Delmont Mine book no. 1482, room book (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Delmont Mine; Delmont Mine # 1, book no. 1250, room book (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Dickson Mine book no. 82, 212 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Dickson Mine book no. 315, Partridge Mine, levels; Dickson Mine book no. 336, transit notes (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Dickson Mine book no. 356, room book; Dickson Mine book no. 965; Outside notes, Division No. 1; Partridge Mine (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Dickson Mine book no. 965; Outside notes, Division No. 1; Partridge Mine, Dickson Mine book no. 1115 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Dickson Mine book no. 1306, 1307 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Dickson Mine book no. 1367, levels; Dickson Mine book no. 1368, levels; Margerum Mine (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Dickson Mine book no. 1507, 1560, room notes (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Dickson Mine book no. 1562; Dickson Strip Mine book no. 1723,; Montour No. 9 Strip Mine, Moon Run Strip Mine (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 1, Channel sample book no. 1, 25-118; Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Coal Field book no. 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Field topography book no. 1; Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine property book no. 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 1, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 1, manholes (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 1, Old 10-08-01; Dilworth Mine; Outside Longwell Mine profile book no. 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 1, sumps; Dilworth Mine, Ten Mile Creek Mine # 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Dilworth Mine, topography book no. 1; Dilworth Mine, town site No. 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Dilworth Mine; Triangulation, Ten Mile Creek Mine # 1; Dilworth Mine, Vertical cross section book no. 1,; Shaft No. 5 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 1A, topography book; Dilworth Mine book no. 1A; Track chutes off Jefferson Mine mains south and miscellaneous levels (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Dilworth Mine, Channel sample book no. 2, 119-Start; Dilworth Mine; Jefferson Field topography book no. 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine property book no. 2; Dilworth Mine, level book no. 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 2, New 10-09-01; Dilworth Mine, Profile book no. 2, outside longwall (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Dilworth Mine, Ten Mine Creek Mine # 2; Dilworth Mine book no. 2, town site (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 2A; Profile, Storage units and belts, Miscellaneous; Dilworth Mine, Channel sample book 3, 198-275 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine Property book no. 3,; Jefferson Mine book no. 3, topography (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 3, level book; Dilworth Mine, Profile book no. 3, outside longwall (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth Mine, Ten Mile Creek Mine # 3; Dilworth Mine book no. 3, topography (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth Mine, Channel sample book 4, 276 – 352; Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Coal Field topography book no. 4 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine property book no. 4; Dilworth Mine book no. 4; Outside levels (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth Mine, Ten Mile Creek Mine # 4; Dilworth Mine book no. 4, topography (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth Mine, Channel sample book 5, 353 –; Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine property book no. 5 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 5, outside (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Dilworth Mine, Ten Mile Creek Mine # 5; Dilworth Mine book no. 5, topography (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine property book no. 6; Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine topography (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 6, outside; Dilworth Mine book no. 6, topography (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine property book no. 7; Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine topography (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 7, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 7F, longwall profile (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine property book no. 8; Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine topography (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 8, outside; Dilworth Mine book no. 8, topography (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Coal Field topography book no. 9; Cumberland Coal Co., Dilworth Mine, Jefferson Mine property book no. 9 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 9, levels and topography (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 10; Greene County Outside (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 10, Jefferson Mine property book; Jefferson Mine, topography (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 10, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 10, outside (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 10, record book; Dilworth Mine book no. 10, record book and levels (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 10, record room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 10, room book (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 10, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 11; Greene County Outside (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 11, Jefferson Mine property book,; Jefferson Mine, topography (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 11, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 11, outside (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 11, record book; Dilworth Mine book no. 11, room book (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 11, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 11, topography (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 11, transit (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 12; Greene County Outside (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 12, Jefferson Mine property book,; Jefferson Mine, topography (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 12, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 12, outside (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 12, records (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 12, room book (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 12, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 13 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 13; Greene County Outside; Jefferson Mine property book (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 13, Jefferson Mine, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 13, levels (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 13, outside; Dilworth Mine book no. 13, record book (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 13, record book; Dilworth Mine book no. 13, room book (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 13, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 13, topography (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 14; Greene County Outside; Dilworth Mine book no. 14, Jefferson Mine property book (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 14; Jefferson Topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 14, levels (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 14, record book (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 14, record book (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 14, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 14, topography (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 14A, book no. 15 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 15; Greene County Outside; Dilworth Mine book no. 15, Jefferson Mine property book (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 15, Jefferson Mine topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 15, levels (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 15, record room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 15, room book (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 15, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 16 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 16, Jefferson Mine, topography (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 16, record room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 16, room book (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 16, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 17 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth Mine book no.17, Jefferson Mine, topography (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 17, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 17, room record (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 17, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 18 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 18, Jefferson Mine, topography (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 18, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 18, topography (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 19 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 19; Greene County Outside; Dilworth Mine book no. 19, room book (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 19, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 20 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 20, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 20, room book (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 20, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 21 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 21, record book; Dilworth Mine book no. 21, room book (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 21, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 22; Greene County Outside (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 22, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 22, room book (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 22, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 23, levels (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 23, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 23, topography (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 24, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 24, room book (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 24, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 25, levels (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 25, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 25, topography (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 26, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 26, room book (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 26, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 27 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 27, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 27, topography (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 28, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 28, room book (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 28, topography; Dilworth Mine book no. 29, levels (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 29, room book; Dilworth Mine book no. 29, topography (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 30, levels; Dilworth Mine book no. 30, room book (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Dilworth Mine book no. 31, levels; Dilworth Mine, unnumbered book (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth Mine; Dilworth Mine, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth Mine, 1991; Dilworth Mine, March 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth Mine, March 1995; Dilworth Mine, longwall profile 3F-4F (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth Mine, longwall profile 5F-6F; Dilworth Mine, main line belt (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth Mine, mains (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth Mine, mains (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Dilworth Mine, outside; Dilworth Mine, outside level book (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Dilworth Mine, outside miscellaneous; Dilworth Mine, topography, Jefferson Mine property book (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Dorothy Mine, Monastery Mine, Unity Mine, Duquesne Mine, levels (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Duquesne Mine, levels, Eclipse Mine book no. 31 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Eclipse Mine book no. 747, outside notes (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Eclipse Mine book no. 1182, 1216 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Eclipse Mine book no. 1217, 1221 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Eclipse Mine book no. 1291, levels; Eclipse Mine book no. 1320, room notes (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Eclipse Mine book no. 1326; Eclipse Mine book no. 1524, room notes (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Eleanor Mine book no. 46, Smock Hill Mine, Eleanor Mine book no. 93, Grindstone Mine (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Eleanor Mine book no. 98, Eleanor Mine book no. 253, Hanna Mine, levels (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Elizabeth Mine book no. 582; Outside levels; Painter Mine, Elkins Mine book no. 263 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Elkins Mine book no. 1102, Elkins Mine, levels (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Elkins Mine, property notes, Ella Mine book no. 670 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Ella Mine book no. 791; Outside notes, Division No. 12; Gallatin Mine surface, Manown Mine, Sunnyside Mine (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Emerald Mine book no. 1, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey book; Emerald Mine book no. 2, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey book (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Emerald Mine book no. 3, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey book; Emerald Mine book no. 4, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey book (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Emerald Mine book no. 5, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey book; Emerald Mine book no. 6, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey book (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Emerald Mine book no. 7, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey book; Emerald Mine book no. 8, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey book (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Emerald Mine book no. 201, levels, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey; Emerald Mine book no. 202, levels, Jones & Laughlin, Vesta survey (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Enterprise Mine book no. 5, 19 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Equitable Mine book no. 2, 112 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Equitable Mine book no. 438, 682; Outside notes, Division No. 7 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Equitable Mine book no. 682; Outside notes, Division No. 7; Equitable Mine book no. 789; Outside notes; Property surveys, Lines and levels (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Equitable Mine book no. 789; Outside notes; Property surveys, Lines and levels; Equitable Mine book no. 822, outside (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Equitable Mine book no. 822, outside; Equitable Mine book no. 1137, Webster Mine (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Equitable Mine book no. 1138, 1280 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Equitable Mine book no. 1388, miscellaneous notes; Equitable Mine book no. 1399 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Equitable Mine book no. 1445, levels; Equitable Mine book no. 1453, room notes (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Essen Mine # 1, # 2, book no. 71; Essen Mine # 1, book no. 88 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Essen Mine # 2, # 3, book no. 183; Essen Mine # 2, # 3, book no. 283, levels (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Essen Mine # 2, book no. 308, room book; Essen Mine # 2, book no. 326 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Essen Mine # 2, book no. 1031; Essen Mine # 3, book no. 333 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Essen Mine # 3, book no. 338, room book; Essen Mine # 3, book no. 1032, levels (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Essen Mine # 3, book no. 1139, Morgan Mine; Essen Mine # 3, book no. 1264, room book (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Essen Mine # 3, book no. 1282; Essen Mine # 3, book no. 1318, levels (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Essen Mine # 3, book no. 1423, room notes; Essen Mine # 3, book no. 1479 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Essen Mine # 3, book no. 1489, levels; Euclid Mine book no. 45, Port Royal Mine (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Euclid Mine book no. 399, 400 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Euclid Mine book no. 401, levels; Euclid Mine book no. 847; Outside surveys; Property surveys; Eureka Mine, Waverly Mine (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Euclid Mine book no. 847; Outside notes; Property surveys; Eureka Mine book no. 4, Waverly Mine; Eureka Mine book no. 28, Waverly Mine surface (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Eureka Mine book no. 146, 173, Waverly Mine (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Eureka Mine book no. 380, 1092 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Eureka Mine book no. 1253, room book; Eureka Mine book no. 1254, levels (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Eureka Mine book no. 1330, 1336 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Eureka Mine # 1, # 2, book no. 130; Fairhaven Mine book no. 195; Coalfields, Property lines (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Fairhaven Mine book no. 239, room notes; Fairhaven Mine book no. 388 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Fairhaven Mine book no. 1010, levels; Fairhaven Mine book no. 1053, room notes (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Fairhaven Mine book no. 1283; Fayette City Mine book no. 1201 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Fayette City Mine book no. 1207, 1228 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Fayette City Mine book no. 1240; Federal Mine book no. 346; Lake Superior Mine, levels (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Federal Mine # 2, book no. 79, 1073 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Federal Mine # 2, book no. 1348; Federoff Mine book no. 1715, North Star Mine (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Fidelity Mine book no. 95; First Pool Mine book no. 126 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - First Pool Mine book no. 196, room notes; First Pool Mine book no. 214 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - First Pool Mine book no. 451; First Pool Mine book no. 471, room book (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - First Pool Mine book no. 472, levels; First Pool Mine book no. 518 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - First Pool Mine book no. 701; Outside notes, Division No. 5; Lewis Run; Property and land tract levels (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - First Pool Mine book no. 1008 and one unnumbered book (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - First Pool Mine # 1, book nos. 1057, 1177 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - First Mine # 2, book no. 393, 1009 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - First Pool Mine # 2, book no. 1242, 1243 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - First Pool Mine # 2, book no. 1376, room book; First Pool Mine # 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - First Pool Mine # 4, # 6 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - First Pool Mine # 10, book no. 360; Forest Hill Mine book no. 301; Division No. 8 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Forest Hill Mine book no. 1052, levels; Forest Hill Mine book no. 1068 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Forest Hill Mine book no. 1157, 1232 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Forest Hill Mine book no. 1347, levels; Forest Hill Mine book no. 1354 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Forest Hill Mine book no. 1464, levels; Forest Hill Mine book no. 1490, general outside notes (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Forest Hill Mine book no. 1531, one unnumbered book (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Forest Hill Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Fort Pitt Mine book no. 34, 100 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Fort Pitt Mine book no. 1065, 1696; Stripping Operations, Panhandle Division; Margerum Mine, Montour Mine, Montour Mine # 9 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Gallatin Mine book no. 839; Outside notes, Division No. 12; Manown Mine, Sunnyside Mine; Property surveys, Gas well locations (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Gallatin Mine book no. 850; Outside notes; Property lines and elevations (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Gallatin Mine book no. 1204, 1210 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Gallatin Mine book no. 1231; Gallatin Mine book no. 1296, room notes (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Gallatin Mine book no. 1382; Gallatin Mine book no. 1460, levels (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Gallatin Mine book no. 1526, inside notes; Gastonville Mine # 2, book no. 140 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Germania Mine book no. 209, Gilmore Mine book no. 1485 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Glenshaw Mine book no. 94, Glenshaw Mine (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Glenshaw Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Gospel Mine book no. 1391, Grant Mine book no. 204 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Grant Mine book no. 343, levels; Grant Mine book no. 382 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Grant Mine book no. 1126; Grant Mine book no. 1259, levels (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Greek Mine book no. 490, Miscellaneous notes; Midland Mine # 1, Union Mine, Allison Mine, Boon; Mine, Midland Mine, Grindstone Mine book no. 18 (Box 26, Folder 6)